我的寶寶怎么會早到
Mnh! How can my babies be early?!
我什么事都沒早過
I've never been early to anything!
也許他們不是我的娃
Maybe they're not mine!
我可對你一直都很忠貞
I've always been faithful to you!
使勁啊 靠
Push, damn it!
我不要今天再失去一個孩子了
I'm not losing another baby today.
心臟驟停
Cardiac arrest.
急救車
Crash cart!
電擊可能會要了孩子的命
The shock could kill the baby!
這是沒有辦法的辦法了
That's something I'll just have to live with.
也許我們該把電視關掉
Maybe we could turn off the TV?
離手
Clear!
伙計們 我恐怕得告訴你們一些壞消息
Well, folks, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
天哪 不要
Oh, my God, no.
不 不是 沒有那么糟糕
N-No, not that bad.
我很抱歉 剛才我沒過腦子
I'm sorry. I did not think that through.
你今天不會生產
No, you're not giving birth today.
剛才你經歷的被稱作假宮縮
You've had false contractions, known as Braxton Hicks.
很常見的
It's very common.
那意味著我會什么時候生呢
Uh, so what does that mean timing-wise?
不一定
It's no indication.
可能是現在起五周后
It could be five weeks from now,
也可能是現在起五小時后
could be five hours from now.
我建議你和你老公回家
I suggest you and your husband go home,
趁你還可以的時候多睡會兒
get some sleep while you still can.
我們還沒結婚 只是情侶
Oh, we're not married. We're just lovers.
嘔
Ugh! Yuck.
她討厭那個詞
She hates that word.
我也覺得惡心
Grosses me out, too,
我可是看過無數產后護理慘況的人呢
and I spend a lot of my time covered in afterbirth.
一切都還好吧
Everything okay?
感覺很怪
Um... that was weird.
你是說那對抱著全尺寸嬰兒的侏儒嗎
Those little people with the full-size baby?
不是 是醫生說你是我老公這件事
No, when the doctor called you my husband.
人們都會下意識覺得吧
Well, people are gonna assume --
不是... 感覺很奇怪是因為我...
No, it -- it was weird because I...
喜歡這個稱呼
liked it.
真的嗎 因為我可能求婚過六次了
Seriously? Because I proposed, like, six times.
我知道 我只是...
I know. I just --
它在當時看起來太過時了
It seemed so old-fashioned at the time,
但是當我想到孩子們要出生的時候
but when I thought that the babies were coming,
我...
I-I...
你是要說出我認為你將要說的話了嗎
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
我需要一點幫助
I'm gonna need a little help here.
好了
Okay.
行了 我好了
Okay, we're good.
迪蘭·星塵·馬歇爾 你愿意...
Dylan Stardust Marshall, will you --
要倒了要倒了 好吧
Oh! Going over. Okay. Okay.
我很好 我很好 沒事
I'm fine. I'm fine. It's okay.
你愿意娶我嗎
Will you marry me?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
這跟我想象中的場景一模一樣
This is exactly how I imagined it.
我進不去
I can't get in!
該死 小卡 我們一定要搶到票
Damn it, Cam! We need those tickets!
-加油 刷新 -我在刷新了
- Come on, refresh. - I am!
-使出吃奶的勁兒刷新 -我在了
- Refresh like your life depends on it! - I am!
今晚是《蘇菲的抉擇:音樂劇》的
Tonight is the L.A. Premiere
洛杉磯首映式
of "Sophie's Choice: The Musical."
票在頃刻之間就賣光了
And it sold out in seconds,
但是劇院保留了一些很棒的座位
but the theater reserved a few amazing house seats
可以網上抽簽獲取
for an online lottery.
有謠言稱
And there's a rumor
梅麗爾·斯特里普也會去觀演
Meryl Streep is going to be in the audience.
-不敢相信 -真得為那個
- Oh, my God. - You have to
扮演蘇菲的女演員默哀
feel for that poor actress playing Sophie.
就像我在鮑勃·麥基面前縫制戲服一樣
It'd be like me sewing costumes in front of Bob Mackie.
現在為您頒發世上最基發言獎 得獎人是...
And the award for the gayest thing ever said goes to...
-我進去了 -真的嗎
- I'm in! - You are?!
-我們有座位啦 -蒼天啊
- We have seats! - Oh, my God!
-集中注意力 -好了
- Focus, focus. - Okay, all right.
好了 這邊是付款倒計時
Okay, it's one of those ticking clock things.
那很好 我只需找到我的信用卡
That's fine. We just need my...credit card.
我的錢包呢 我的錢包 錢包
Where's my wallet? Where -- Where's my wall--
-我的錢包去哪兒了 -不是吧 又這樣
- Where's my wallet?! - Seriously? Again?
小卡 你得把它放在一個固定的地方
Cam, you have to leave it in one place!
我跟你說過一千遍了
I told you a thousand times!
非得現在說教嗎
Really? Now?
行了 就用你的信用卡吧
Okay, just use your credit card.
怪了
That's weird.
好了 我要吐了 我要吐了
Okay. I'm gonna be sick. I'm gonna be sick!
-來 用我的吧 -謝謝 甜心
- Here -- use mine. - Oh! Thank you, sweetie.
好了 好了 行了
Okay. Okay. All right.
這是什么標志[征兆]嗎
Is this a sign?
是啊 預示著我們要去看演出了
Yes! We are meant to see the show!
不是 是檢測買票機器人的驗證圖
No, it's one of those CAPTCHA things.
這是個路標嗎
Is that a road sign?!
-是的 -我不知道
- Yes! - I don't know.
是的
Yes.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God!
謝謝 甜心寶貝 你救了我們
Oh, thank you, sweetie. You saved us.
沒事 我需要刷卡換里程
It's fine. I needed the miles.
謝謝你
Thank you.
她要去哪里
Where's she off to?
-我肯定沒事的 -好吧
- I'm sure it's fine. - Okay.
這件怎么樣
How about this one?
你看起來太美了
You look gorgeous.
現在 記住...
Now, remember --
好了 這又不是我第一次
Okay, this is not my first time
要去哄你的商業伙伴了
impressing your business associates.
我知道怎么做
I know the drill.
笑他們的笑話 撫摸他們的手臂
Laugh at their jokes, touch their arms...
然后如果他在地板上撒尿
Yeah, and if he pees on the floor,
別太當回事兒
don't make a big deal out of it.
怎么回事
What is happening?
我退出了衣柜事業
I quit the closet game
成為了高端逗趣狗床的尖端人物
to become the king of high-end, whimsical dog beds.
今天 為了推廣它們 我要接待
And to market them today, I'm hosting
社交媒體網紅 亞瑟乖仔
social-media influencer Arthur Goodboy.
這只小帥狗
This little stud
在網上有超過五百萬的粉絲
has over 5 million followers on the Instagram.
一張他與產品的照片就能改天換地
One photo of him with a product can be a game-changer.
你讓我為一只狗換了三次衣服
You made me change three times for a dog?
他甚至看不到這個顏色
He cannot even see this color!
5他們可以感覺到你的努力
They can sense the effort!
歡迎 歡迎 我是杰·普里契特
Welcome! Welcome. I'm Jay Pritchett.
-你好 -這是我老婆歌洛莉亞
- Hello. - This is my wife, Gloria.
你們好
Hello.
奧森·豐特
Orson Funt.
我想大家都認識亞瑟乖仔啦
I'm sure everyone knows Arthur Goodboy.
誰不會呢 我得承認 我有一種遇見巨星的感覺
Who doesn't? And I must admit, I'm a little starstruck.
不必
Don't be.
他跟普通狗一樣 穿毛衣也是一次一條腿啦
He puts on his sweaters one leg at a time.
這是"斯黛拉的狗床"的斯黛拉
And this is Stella of Dog Beds by Stella,
不過大部分設計是我做的
but I do most of the design.
對于非職業選美選手來說 她很漂亮
Well. She is beautiful for a non-pro.
-我能抱抱嗎 -給你 好了
- May I? - Here you go. Yes.
-我能嗎 -當然
- May I? - Oh, yeah.
謝謝 太棒了
Thank you. Oh, yes.
立正 立正
Present! Present.
誰是可愛的女士呀
Who's a lovely lady?
誰是優雅的男孩兒呀 誰是影響人物呀
Who's an elegant boy? Who's an influencer?
你是 你是
Ooh, you are! You are!
誰是影響人物啊 你是
Who's an influencer? You are!
想去看看狗床嗎
You want to see the dog beds?
-想 -跟我來
- Yes. - Follow me.
他是個好爸爸
He's a good father.
先生...
Sir...
狗放在菠蘿里
a dog in a pineapple?
愛了
Love!
我叫它"犬鳳呈祥"
I call that one "Puppy Colada."
得了
Stop!
是啊 得了
Yes, stop.
那你怎么看 咱們能做這筆生意嗎
So, what do you say? Are we in business?
等一下 別著急
Oh, down boy.
在幫你做推薦之前
I like to make sure that Arthur Goodboy
我得確保亞瑟乖仔真的喜歡這件產品
really loves the product before we do any endorsements.
如果我們什么都答應
If we said yes to everything,
那跟網紅暴躁貓那啥都代言的婊子有何分別
then we're no better than that whore Grumpy Cat.
來 試試這個
Here, try this one.
好了 亞瑟乖仔先生
Okay, Mr. Arthur Goodboy.
你何不自己去里面
Why don't you just trot yourself right in there
打個盹兒呢
and take a load off?
他才剛睡過一陣子 所以...
You know, he just woke up from a nap, so...
他可能過幾小時才會想休息
he will probably tucker out in a couple of hours.
但沒關系 反正我也沒有別的事
It's cool, 'cause I have nowhere I need to be.
真"意外"啊
You don't say.
里面真寬敞
Oh, it's spacious.
海莉
Haley?
我在這
Over here!
媽沒跟你一起出來吧
Mom's not with you, right?
沒有
No.
出什么事了
What's going on?
你已經懷孕了
What could you have possibly done
還能有什么更嚴重的
that's worse than getting pregnant?
迪蘭和我要私奔結婚
Well, Dylan and I are eloping,
我們想讓你去作見證
and we want you to be the witness.
我的天 我愿意
Oh, my God! Yes!
我都無法形容這讓我覺得自己多特別了
Oh, I can't even tell you how special this makes me feel.
我不會告訴任何人 我
I will not tell anyone. I --
等等 為什么私奔 為什么不辦婚禮
Wait. Why eloping? Why not a wedding?
我們只想簡單快速地結婚
We just want it to be simple and quick.
不想有各種大戲
And no drama.
-那老媽是肯定不能帶上了 -是啊
- Guess that eliminates Mom. - Yeah.
什么不能帶上老媽
What eliminates Mom?
是這樣的 是這樣的 說來有趣
You know, uh -- You know, it-it's so funny when --
當人們 做出這種有趣的事
when people do such, um, funny --
其實三言兩語就能說清
You know, the story is so short,
-但又說來話長 -夠了 夠了
- but it-it-it would be so long -- - Enough, enough.
我看不下去了
I cannot watch this.
我覺得她要鋪墊出個故事了呢
I felt like she was building to something.
迪蘭和我要去法院結婚
Dylan and I are going to the courthouse to get married.
我們不是不想帶你
It's nothing personal, you know?
只不過 我們現在最不想要的
It's just...right now, the last thing we want
就是最后搞成了大型婚禮
is it to turn into a big production.
親愛的 假如這是你想要的
Well, honey, if that's what you want,
作為你母親 雖然這顯然讓我十分痛苦
as your mother, obviously, it's incredibly painful,
但你完全不必擔心
but that-that's none of your concern.
我只希望你的婚禮
I just hope you have a wedding that's every bit
能和我一直以來想象得一樣美好感人
as wonderful and beautiful as I always imagined.
盡管我不能像想象中那樣出席
You know -- when I was gonna be part of it.
我就知道她不會介意
I knew she'd be cool.
-是啊 -我們走
- Yeah! - Let's roll.
老媽看起來挺受打擊的
Mom seemed pretty bummed about it,
可這是我們想要的
but, you know, this is what we want.
沒錯
Totally!
媽蛋
Damn it!
你怎能這樣對你母親
How could you do this to your mother?
他們怎么這么慢
What's taking them so long?
就是說啊 婚禮的主角又不是他們
I know. It's, like, this wedding isn't about them.
是你和迪蘭 還有我
It's about you and Dylan and me!
來了
Coming!
真抱歉
So sorry.
別擔心 海莉
And don't worry, Haley.
我保證你幾乎不會注意到我們在場
I promise you will hardly know we are there at all.
搞什么 你們穿得比我還正式
What? You're dressed nicer than me.
我原本不想說什么 但你確定
Well, I wasn't gonna say anything, but are you sure
你在這個特別的日子就穿這身衣服嗎
that's the outfit you want for your special day?
這是海莉的婚禮 她想穿得多難看都隨她
It's Haley's wedding. She can dress as bad as she wants.
沒錯
Right.
誰死了
Who died?
海莉和迪蘭要結婚了
Haley and Dylan are getting married.
穿成這樣結婚嗎
Dressed like that?
現在我還得帶上盧克
Now I have to invite Luke?
你不想帶就不帶
Not if you don't want to.
你真會說話
This feels great.
好吧 就帶上盧克 不能再加人了
Okay, that is it. Luke, but no one else.
我媽發現你父母會出席
Hey, so, my mom found out your parents are coming,
因為我告訴她了 現在她也正趕來
'cause I told her, and now she's on her way.
我外公也來
And Grandpa's coming.
你們會很喜歡他的
You guys are gonna love him.
但假如他叫你們殺了他 別下手
Oh, but if he asks you to kill him, don't.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
人太多了
That is a lot of people
法院那沒有人情味的小房間擠不下
for a small, impersonal room at the courthouse,
我們也是這么想的
and we are on the same page.
所以 為什么不在這結婚
So...why don't we just do it here?
我有證婚人資格 我可以主持婚禮
I'm ordained. I can perform the ceremony.
這個主意太好了
That is such a great idea!
那樣的話 又簡單又私人化
That way, it's easy and intimate.
這正是你想要的 不是嗎
I mean, that's what you wanted, right?
你們先去法院
So, go down to the courthouse,
領結婚證 然后回來
get your marriage license, come back here,
我們都在這等著
and we'll all be waiting.
好吧 我們立刻就得去
Fine. But let's go now.
我餓死了 法院的小賣部
I'm starving, and they make a great soft pretzel
有特別好吃的軟椒鹽餅
at the courthouse snack shop.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我還是可以私奔的
I can still elope.
別壞了我的好事
Don't you ruin this for me.
無所謂 無所謂
It's fine. It's fine.
等等
Wait.
假如迪蘭的外公要來
If Dylan's bringing his grandfather,
我們也必須邀請我爸和歌洛莉亞 不是嗎
that means we have to invite Dad and Gloria, right?
我想是的
I think so, yeah.
但他八成不會來 杰討厭臨時邀約
But he probably won't show. Jay hates last-minute plans.
他會說"老天 他們怎么不私奔"
He'll be like, "Oh, geez, why don't they just elope?"
外公你來啦
Grandpa?
誰是乖乖仔
Who's a goody-woody boy?
誰是犯困的乖仔
Who's a sleepy boy?
沒想到我會說這種話
I never thought I'd say this,
但我想念杰傷人的大男子主義
but I miss Jay's toxic masculinity.
至少他不是你親爹
At least he's not your real father.
-我來接 我接 -我來接
- I'll get it! I got it! - I'll get it!
-你好 -歌洛莉亞
- Hello? - Hey, Gloria.
海莉和迪蘭決定今天下午結婚
Haley and Dylan decided to get married this afternoon,
我知道老爸要談狗床生意
and I know Dad's got that dog-bed thing,
所以不必有壓力
so absolutely no pressure.
好的 我們會盡快趕過去
Yes. We will be there as soon as we can.
杰 很遺憾不得不打斷
Jay, I am so sorry to break up
這個非常有趣非常正常的聚會
this really fun and super normal party,
但迪蘭和海莉決定現在結婚
but Dylan and Haley decided to get married right now,
克萊爾想讓我們過去
and Claire wants us there.
老天 他們怎么不私奔
Oh, geez, why don't they just elope?
其實亞瑟乖仔很喜歡婚禮
Actually, Arthur Goodboy loves weddings,
它的粉絲們一直很想看它穿新西裝
and his followers have been dying to see him in his new tux.
我可以帶個狗床 以防它想休息
I-I can bring a bed in case he gets tired.
快看 有人心動了
Ooh, look. Somebody's got a crush.
斯黛拉小姐可否賞光
Would Miss Stella do us the honor
陪亞瑟乖仔一同出席婚禮
of escorting Arthur Goodboy to the wedding?!
老天 當然 一萬個愿意
Gosh, yes! A thousand times yes!
說出來你肯定不信
Well. You're not gonna believe this.
他們會來
They're coming.
假如他們會來 那我們是不是
Well, if they're coming, does that mean
也得邀請米奇和小卡
we need to invite Mitch and Cam?
想象一下不請的話他們得有多少狗血戲
Imagine the drama if we didn't.
? 我該選擇誰 ?
♪ Who should I choose? ♪
? 選一個都得失去另一個 ?
♪ Either way, I lose ♪
? 我盯著槍扣 ?
♪ I stare at the gun ♪
? 是選我女兒 還是選兒子 ?
♪ Is it daughter, is it son? ♪
? 抉擇 ?
♪ Choices ♪
-? 困難的抉擇 ? -? 抉擇 ?
- ♪ Impossible choices ♪ - ♪ Choices ♪
-? 困難的抉擇 ? -? 困難 ?
- ♪ Impossible choices ♪ - ♪ Impossible ♪
? 抉擇 ?
♪ Choices ♪
這就是為什么我不能邀請朋友來做客
This is why I can't have friends over.
好吧
Okay.
某人因為損人
Somebody just snarked her way
沒有《蘇菲的抉擇》衛衣穿了
out of a "Sophie's Choice" Hoodie!
沒錯
That's right.
克萊爾 什么事
Hey, Claire. What's up?
海莉和迪蘭決定結婚了
So, Haley and Dylan decided to get married,
你們要是不來他們會傷心死的
and they'd be devastated if you weren't there.
當然 我們無論如何也不會錯過
Oh, of course! We wouldn't miss it for the world!
告訴我們什么時候
Just tell us when.
大約一小時后
In about an hour.
我的天 我
Oh, my -- Hey, uh, let --
我稍后給你回電話 好嗎
let me call you right back, okay?
開什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?!
就是說 該怎么辦 音樂劇還是婚禮
I know! What do we do -- a musical or the wedding?
世上沒人被迫面臨過更殘酷的選擇
It's the cruelest decision anyone's ever been forced to make.
-有人嗎 我們來了 -敲敲門
- Hello? We are here! - Knock, knock!
這都是些什么
What is all this?
克萊爾
Hey, Claire.
這位是奧森
This is Orson
而這當然就是亞瑟乖仔
and, of course, Arthur Goodboy.
多謝你邀請我們 我們愛愛情
Thanks for having us. We love love.
爸 能過來私下聊兩句嗎
Dad, can you come over here a second?
斯黛拉 你好啊
Hey, Stella.
聽著 我覺得海莉不會想
So, listen, I don't think Haley
回到有一屋子的陌生人和狗的家
wants to come back to a house full of strangers and dogs.
克萊爾 我得抓住這個機會
Claire, I've got to have this,
而且她都不會感覺到他們在這的
and she's never gonna know they're even here.
好吧 這話說的時機不太好
Okay, that's bad timing.
動起來 動起來 大家都動起來
Okay, okay, let's -- let's go, let's go, let's go.
動起來 來忙活起來
Let's go. Let's get it going.
你們著什么急 我以為你們...
What's your hurry? I thought you...
兩個喜歡婚禮呢
guys love weddings.
你準備說"你們這種人"是不是
You were gonna say "You people," Weren't you?
有證據嗎
Prove it.
我們拿著音樂劇的票
We have theater tickets,
如果現在婚禮開始的話
and if we get this wedding started,
我們還能趕上《蘇菲的抉擇》的開場
we can still make curtain for "Sophie's Choice."
為了看那個音樂劇
I would murder my entire family
我愿意干掉自己全家親友
and all of their friends to see that musical.
這人懂行
This guy gets it.
看看這是誰呀
Look who's here!
別擔心 我穿褲子了
Don't worry. I'm wearing pants.
至少你們看起來是的
As far as you know.
你好啊 弗蘭克
Oh, well, hello, Frank.
謝謝你 差不多算出席了
And thank you for...sort of making it.
-真要這樣嗎 -你邀請了你爸爸
- Really? - Well, you invited your dad.
-我還能不邀請我爸爸嗎 -我不知道了
- What was I supposed to do? - I don't know.
你好啊 這是亞瑟乖仔嗎
Hey! Is that Arthur Goodboy?
我是超級粉絲
Big fan!
早就期待看它穿西裝的樣子了
Been waiting to see him in his tux.
法拉
Farrah.
-菲爾 -很高興見到...
- Phil. - It is so delightful to see --
天啊
Oh. Gosh.
你能相信我們的孩子要結婚了嗎
Can you believe our babies are getting married?
我能
I can.
我在秘魯的一叢篝火里見到了這個景象
I saw it in a vision at a campfire in Peru.
這是我的父親 伯特
This is my father, Bert.
很榮幸能...
Oh, it's such an honor to --
伏特加
Vodka!
好漂亮的裙子
What a lovely dress.
其實這是薩滿教的婚禮禮服
It's actually a shamanic wedding robe
產自南美
from South America.
我每次主持儀式都穿
I wear it at every ceremony I officiate.
這就有點尷尬了
Ohhh. This is awkward.
我要主持儀式
I'm doing the ceremony.
但這是我想了一輩子的事啊
But this is something I've dreamed about all of my lives.
媽 這是什么情況
Mom, what the hell is going on?
寶貝 其實沒有看上去那么糟啦
Oh, honey, honey, it's not as bad as it looks.
你看 還是小規模 又簡潔又...
See, it's still small and simple and --
別幫倒忙
Not helping.
怎么了 我們要在她步向祭壇時奏樂啊
What? We were gonna play her down the aisle.
對 沒有風笛伴奏的婚禮會遭受厄運
Yeah. Bad luck to get married without bagpipes.
我媽的第一個婚禮 沒有風笛
My mom's first wedding -- no bagpipes.
我媽的第二個婚禮 有風笛
My mom's second wedding -- bagpipes.
六個月之后 還沒離婚
Six months later, she's still married.
我的意思是 這就是科學啊
I mean, that's just science.
這又是什么
Now what?
我們需要食物 所以
Oh, well, we needed food, so...
你們好啊 小情侶
Hola, lovebirds.
這真是場災難
Oh, this is a disaster.
我理解 不過我們也沒法選擇兒時的家
I know, but we can't pick our childhood homes.
別擔心 我能解決好一切的
Don't worry. I can fix everything.
不要著急 慢慢去換你的衣服吧
Just take your time changing your clothes.
這就是我要穿的
Oh, this is what I'm wearing.
你太搞笑了
You're hilarious.
讓我見見這對恩愛情侶
Let me see the happy couple.
恭喜你 海莉
Congratulations, Haley.
恭喜你 安迪
Congratulations, Andy.
抱歉 寶貝 我知道你有點生氣
Sorry. Honey, I know you're a little annoyed.
真是不好意思我讓你這么想了
Oh, I'm so sorry I gave you that impression.
我都快氣死了
I'm a lot annoyed.
不過這樣更好
But it's better.
這樣的話 你就能被愛你的人所環繞
This way, you'll be surrounded by people who love you.
就是她
That's her.
恭喜你 我真為你高興
Congratulations! I am so happy for you.
盧克
Luke?
這是安娜貝爾
Uh, this is Annabelle.
我們剛在交友軟件上認識
We just met on Tinder.
不過我們還沒來得及做什么
But we haven't done anything yet.
你們猜怎么著 寶寶們
Guess what, babies.
今天你們能嘗嘗酒的滋味了
You're gonna taste some wine today!
既然婚禮快開始了
So, if we're gonna get this thing started,
你是不是應該上樓換個衣服
maybe you should go up and change, huh?
再說最后一次 這就是我
Oh, for the last time, this is what I'm --
算了 我去換
Screw it. I'm changing.
-不 不用 -不用換 如果那就是
- No, don't - No, don't change, if that's --
-真是的 -對不起 我錯了
- Damn it! What - Sorry. I'm sorry.
歌洛莉亞
Gloria, Gloria.
幫我個忙
Do me a favor.
往我的電視機里放點臘腸
Put some salami in my TV.
不管這是什么的暗號 我都不答應
Whatever that is a code for, the answer is no.
好吧 那我自己來
Okay, fine. I'll do it myself.
拖住奧森一小會兒
Keep Orson occupied for about a minute.
亞瑟乖仔 過來
Arthur Goodboy, come.
奧森先生
Mr. Orson.
我想知道 你生活的一切都是你的狗狗嗎
Um, I need to know -- is your whole life your dog?
不不 我對單人喜劇也有所涉獵
Oh, no. I also dabble in stand-up comedy.
我以前會把自己的段子給亞瑟乖仔試講一遍
In fact, I used to try out all of my material on Arthur Goodboy
直到后來善待動物組織指控我拿動物做試驗
until I got in trouble with PETA for animal testing.
話說回來 亞瑟去哪了
Speaking of, where is Arthur?
我相信它沒事的
I'm sure he's fine.
亞瑟 亞瑟
Arthur? Arthur?
它在活動室里 狼吞虎咽什么冷切腸
He's in the family room, wolfing down some cold cuts.
不不不 它消化不了那個
No, no, no. He can't digest that.
西裝可是租來的還要還回去
And that tuxedo is rented.
別 等一等
No, please! Wait!
住手
Aah! Stop!
住手 什么 不要
Stop? What, no!
它很喜歡這個床 別啊 它喜歡在里面
He's enjoying the bed. No, he loves it in there.
別說了
Don't.
那個機器人什么都跟我說了
The robot told me everything.
-對不起 但是我以為只要它 -別說了
- Oh, I'm sorry, but I thought once he got - Stop! Unh!
我會待到婚禮結束
I will stay for the wedding
免得不毀掉海爾西和德里克的大喜日子
so as not to ruin Halsey and Derek's special day,
但是我們的合作沒戲了
but this partnership is off.
我這是在做什么
What am I doing?
讓自己丟人現眼
Making a fool of yourself --
你一整天都在這樣
what you have done the whole day.
對 我表現得像個傻瓜
Yeah. I'm acting like an idiot.
這個點子太蠢了
I mean, this was a stupid idea,
在我這把年紀還想重新創業
trying to launch a whole new business at my age.
我還以為會很有意思
I thought it would be fun,
我早就該知道的 我該金盆洗手了
but I should've known I-I need to hang it up.
我想靜靜
I need a second.
狗床確實很滑稽很悲哀
Dog beds are ridiculous and sad.
但是對杰來說很重要
But they're important to Jay.
我想愛一個人就意味著你也需要尊重他們
So I guess that loving someone means that you have to respect
愚蠢又令人惡心的夢想
their idiotic, nauseating dreams.
你好 老兄弟
Hey, old-timer.
我喜歡你的輪椅
I dig those wheels.
為什么這個吸塵器在跟我說話
Why is this vacuum cleaner talking to me?!
我們剩的時間不多了
Okay, we are definitely cutting it close,
不過我覺得我們能趕上的
but I think we're gonna make it.
你知道嗎 按傳統的婚禮儀式
You know, it's just that, uh, traditionally,
是新娘的爸爸對這些事情說了算
the father of the bride calls the shots at these things.
老天爺 菲爾
Oh, my goddess, Phil.
一定要這樣的話 那我們徹底回到傳統婚禮好了
By all means, let's return to traditional weddings.
或許你愿意討論一下海莉的嫁妝
Perhaps you'd like to discuss the matter of Haley's dowry.
你們準備陪嫁牲畜還是土地呢
Are you prepared to offer livestock or land?
法拉 如果這是在你們的
Farrah, I would defer to you
圓頂帳篷里我會聽你的
if this were happening in your yurt.
好吧
Fine.
我們來擲橡子決定吧
We'll settle this over a game of acorns.
伸出你的手來
Put out your hands.
橡子 說話吧
Acorns, speak.
對不起 菲爾
Oh. Sorry, Phil.
三局兩勝
Best of 3.
這是在干什么
What am I doing?
好了 你們倆 停下來
Okay, both of you, stop!
你們兩個都主持 行嗎
You can both officiate, all right?
但是那不會花兩倍的時間嗎
Yeah, but won't that take twice as long?
不管誰主持 能不能抽出點時間
Uh, whoever's officiating, if you can carve out some time
讓我讀一下我寫的詩
for a poem I've written.
這是《貝奧武夫》和《電子情書》的結合版
It's sort of a "Beowulf" Meets "You've Got Mail."
天啊 求求不要讀詩了 別啊
Oh, God, no! No poems! No!
-沒人想聽詩 -誰要聽啊
- Nobody wants a poem! - No one wants that!
-快點吧 流程走下去 -繼續下去
- Come on! Let's move this thing along! - Get it going!
你們得交出《蘇菲的抉擇》票
You need to give your "Sophie's Choice" ticket
給那個養狗怪人
to the dog weirdo.
我爸居然想看音樂劇嗎
My dad wants to see a musical?
不是 是另一個養狗怪人
No, the other dog weirdo.
你們沒看到他聽到時有多興奮嗎
Didn't you see how excited he got when he heard about it?
但這事絕對沒門 您慢走
Yeah, well, that's not happening. No, thank you.
想想這些年來
Think about all the sacrifices
你父親為你做的犧牲啊
that your father has made for you.
但我真的不在意啊
Oh, I just don't care.
你們反正也來不及趕到
You're not gonna make it anyways.
我們能趕到 婚禮馬上就要開始了
Y-Yes, we are, 'cause the wedding's about to start.
-他們來啦 -是嗎
- Here they come. - Is it?
不好意思
Excuse me.
在我們開始這場美好的儀式之前
Um, before we start this beautiful ceremony,
我們在座各位何不輪流一下
why don't we go around the room
聊聊這場婚禮對他們代表的意義
and talk about what this wedding means to us?
我想應該沒人想被拱上臺做出發言吧
Yeah, I don't think anybody wants to be put on the spot.
就繼續把婚禮流程走完吧
Let's just get on with the wedding.
對我來說 婚姻不只是兩個人心的聯結
To me, a marriage is not just the joining of two hearts.
還是兩個家庭合而為一
It's the melding of families.
請聽我說這句
And can I just say this --
-不聽 坐下 -不聽 坐下
- No! Sit down! - No! Sit down!
去吧 去吧 這就對啦
Go on, go on. There you go.
撒的是 泡沫塑料嗎
Are those... packing peanuts?
我只有十分鐘準備 還沒經費
I had 10 minutes and no budget.
-真的要發生了呢 -是啊
- This is happening. - Yep.
這只狗在對斯黛拉做什么啊
What's this dog doing to Stella?
壞狗狗 不許日
Bad dog! No humping!
不許羞辱他 這是她的錯
Don't shame him! That's her fault.
她自己在他臉上扭屁股
She's wagging her hips in his face!
那是她腰不好
That's her dysplasia.
而且都2019年了
And it's 2019.
他怎么可以強搶民女呢
What he did is not okay!
糟糕 我是不是在動啊
Uh-oh. Am I moving?
好像有東西卡住了
Something's stuck!
-菲爾 我跌倒了 -看 就是這樣
- Phil, I'm falling! - See, this -- this --
這就是為什么我不想請人來
this is why I didn't want anyone here!
這就是為什么我想私奔
This is why I wanted to elope!
海莉 我知道你不高興 但他們是你的家人啊
Haley, I know you're upset, but this is your family.
你誰啊
Who are you?!
好 夠了 夠了
Okay, enough! Enough.
迪蘭 海莉 現在都到廚房來
Dylan, Haley, in the kitchen -- now!
鞋真好看
Nice shoes!
很抱歉 各位
I am, uh, so sorry, folks.
可能 可能需要大家等一小段時間
This is -- This is gonna take a little while.
或許艾麗克斯和比爾可以給大家奏點音樂
Maybe Alex and Bill can play something.
-不要 -別了
- No! - No!
-我們是趕不上了對吧 -好吧 不行
- We're not gonna make it, are we? - Okay, no.
我們估計來不及 感覺就沒戲了
We're not gonna make it! It -- It doesn't look like it.
不好意思
Hey, um...
我爸爸希望你能收下這些票
Hi. My dad wanted you to have these tickets.
我勒個大丹犬 太謝謝你們了
Great Danes! Thank you!
別著急 你還有一件事情沒做呢
Not so fast. You still have something to do.
聽 聽我說
Listen. Listen to me.
媽 我不想聽
I don't want to hear it, Mom.
跑吧
Run.
-什么 -是的
- What?! - Yeah.
很抱歉事情沒按我們料想中的發展
We're really sorry that this all got away from us.
但我們真正在乎的是你開心
But all we care about is that you're happy.
而你應該擁有你想要的婚禮
And you should have the wedding you want.
你媽媽說得對
Your mom's right.
我們也私定終身過 現在想起來
We eloped, and I still think of it
還覺得那是我人生中最美好的一段時光之一
as one of the best days of my life.
到現在還感覺那是我們倆最后獨處的日子
It still seems like the last day we were alone.
這...
That's...
小寶貝
Oh, honey.
你們四個人快上路吧
The four of you better get going, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我的寶貝們啊
Ohh, my babies.
愛你們
I love you, guys.
再見 再見啦
Bye. Bye.
你還好嗎
You okay?
其實不好
Not really, no.
我好難過自己不能在場陪伴
I hate that we're not gonna be there.
我一直覺得她結婚時我一定會在場
I always assumed we would be at her wedding.
這樣是不是很自私啊
Is that selfish?
當然不
No.
這樣才公平啊
It's only fair.
她也參加了我們的婚禮
She was at ours.
是啊
Mm. She was.
快看
Look at this.
他在一分鐘前發了文 已經有五千贊了
He posted one minute ago. It's already got 5,000 likes.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我愛你嘛
I love you.
而比狗床還不性感的 就是半途而廢了
And the only thing less sexy than a dog bed is a quitter,
我可不想嫁給半途而廢的人
and I didn't marry a quitter.
我娶了個天使
I married an angel.
是的
Yes, you did!
能請大家注意聽我說一下嗎
Could I have everyone's attention? Um...
我想說在場的大多數人
I just want to say that most of you
都對我們十分重要
are very important to us.
但婚禮取消了 感謝你們的到來
But the wedding's off, and thanks for coming.
-什么 -你耍我們啊
- What?! - You got to be kidding me!
我真的服了 我們這是血海深仇
This is an outrage. I will never forgive you.
你們倆有興趣給在場各位唱個歌嗎
Perhaps the two of you would like to sing a song?
? 抉擇 困難 ?
♪ Choices, impossible ♪
-? 抉擇 ? -? 抉擇 困難 ?
- ♪ Choices ♪ - ♪ Choices, impossible ♪
-? 抉擇 ? -? 為什么有那么多 ?
- ♪ Choices ♪ - ♪ Why are there so many ♪
? 聲音 ?
♪ Voices ♪
? 抉擇與聲音與聲音 ?
♪ Choices and voices and voices ♪
老媽 老爸
Mom? Dad?
親愛的
Oh, honey.
你回來啦 怎么樣了
Hey. How did it go?
我們最后沒結婚
Uh, we...didn't go through with it.
什么
What?
我們當時在24小時證婚教堂
We were at this 24-hour chapel,
當時叫到我們了 但...
and they called our names, but...
但就是有哪里感覺怪怪的
something about it just didn't feel right.
親愛的 沒關系
Sweetheart, it's okay.
時候到了你自己會知道的
You'll know when it's the right time.
所以我來了這里
That's why I'm here.
我想了想你們說過的話
I thought about what you said
就是我應該擁有自己想要的婚禮
about how I should have the wedding that I want.
我想要的婚禮是你們在場的那種
Well, the wedding that I want has you guys there.
就像婚禮鹿角一樣
And, like the nuptial antler,
你們的婚姻將堅固無比
your bond will never be broken.
你來收尾吧 菲爾
Take us home, Phil.
所以
And so,
我以無痛征婚網所賦予我的權力
by the powers vested in me by NoPainOrdain.Com,
我宣布你 迪蘭
I pronounce you, Dylan...
與你 海莉
and you, Haley...
正式成為
husband...
夫妻
...and wife.
快親新娘啊
Hey! Kiss her already!
天啊
Oh, my God.
你想跟我談事情嗎
You want to talk to me.
是啊 有件事這幾天一直讓我煩心
Yeah. Um... it's been bothering me the last few days.
就是他們本來想終身 迪蘭沒有先來
Since they were gonna elope, Dylan never came to me
求我同意讓他娶我女兒
and ask for Haley's hand in marriage.
是啊
Yeah.
然后我想到了
Well, then it occur to me that
我跟克萊爾也私定終身了
since Claire and I eloped
我當年也沒有正式去請求讓我娶你女兒
I never offically asked you for her hand in marriage.
-所以呢... -那你問我啊
- So ah... - So ask me.
行
Okay.
杰
Jay,
我非常愛你女兒
I love your daughter very much.
我想請求你...
And I would like your...
不行
Nop.
很會搞笑
That's very funny.
但說真的 我很希望有你的同意與祝福
But seriously, I would very much like your blessing.
抱歉 但我心里有些疑慮 我不同意
Sorry, I've got several conserns. I'm not onboard.
你知道這只是走個過場吧
You realise this is just a formality.
我和她都結婚要25年了
We've been married for more almost 25 years.
這無數年間都沒有我的祝福
And the entire time without my blessing.
這件事需要我買多少張狗床才能擺平
Ok, how many dog beds is this gonna cost me?
-5張 -3張
- Five. - Three.
-4張 -成交
- Four. - Done.
已祝福
Blessed.